hello hello YouTube universe I did not
record a video yesterday yesterday was
my daughter's first day of kindergarten
and it was awesome but also exhausting
because I have to attend with her this
week and all the times sometimes I feel
like when I'm living my life health with
health when I'm eating well when I'm
exercising and maybe I don't know my
disability maybe I'm like I'm faking it
but over exaggerating it maybe it's not
as bad as I think I never know how I
compared to the rest of the world do I
have less do I actually have less energy
100 people and then I spend the day
sitting on a couch doing nothing but
surrounded by noise and I feel like I
got run over by a truck and did am a
marathon and so today we are going to
the farm part of this school which I'm
super excited by so I get to be outside
around animals which is not as bad as
being around fluorescent lights and in
an enclosed place with sounds but I also
wanted to talk today
I was scared scared to get my hair cut
and every time I go to my hairdresser
she's one of my good friends and Michael
I kind of want this and I kinda and I
just get like short last time I got it
like I'm short but off and that was like
a little edgy for me and this time shoot
anyway so my daughter got her hair cut
and then I got my hair cut and I was
kind of talking about sure she's like
wait are we going short and then anyway
she did my hair and I love it it's like
this is the first time I've loved a
haircut where it's not just like oh I
just got a haircut like it feels I
afraid that Sean got in short hair cuz I
let my hair grow ridiculously for the
ridiculous long time between haircuts to
save money also because I don't have
time for appointments like that even
though I love my friend uncle visit her
for other reasons but not to get my hair
cut and not even expense because she's
not that expensive but finding
yeah sorry once they get my hair cut
short and that like experience when you
first wash it it feels like there's like
some missing uneven commented on that
when I got it done and it doesn't feel
that way
it feels like this is my hair cut like
this is I mean it probably won't have it
for decades this guy probably goes out
of style but who cares about style but
oh it just feels like home like it feels
like it suits my face and my personality
at the moment and why didn't I do it
before but it wasn't supposed to happen
before I probably would have cried if it
happened before just the issue is is
short hair was tied to like bad haircuts
my mom did to us when we were kids and
being called up away or I can picture
it'll be like it's Jubilee binding just
funny now I forgot the haircut I even
said to my daughter like Oh someone like
this I don't think right now but it was
like well it was wet indefinitely so
mine actually mistake me for oh boy and
that feels like that's what I'm looking
for like I'm going for more gender
neutral is what I feel I'm still
figuring out all of my gender stuff
which is actually figuring it out it's
deconstructing all the silly rules and
conditioning we put on girls and boys
and what is true to me Who am I Who am I
not Who am I trying to be not who am i
trying to be to attract a partner or to
be more feminine or more massive and
more anything I'm just me and bit by bit
figuring that out and for the first time
like now that I've got my hair cut I am
like oh I want a new wardrobe I want new
clothes I don't even know what new
clothes I want but like I want them and
that's something different to like I
want to look good and not for anyone
else not even to attract anyone else I
don't even know if I want to attract
anyone no idea
I do build objects a girl but it also
scares me to to death so you know
well most of my life well I look really
tired this is like yeah it's early
we don't believe as early today because
you don't have to catch the bus to the
bus the bus back home and then the other
bus we have two buses instead of four
buses today so yeah I'm just gonna go
hang out with cute animals be with my
child and hopefully let the earth
regenerate me like being in fluorescent
lights and concrete does not even with
amazing humans okay have a good Tuesday
I'm gonna do an extra video this weekend
in order to catch up so that my my
numbers make sense since I missed
yesterday so what is today yes sure the
21st day is the 21st video talking about
haircuts the first day of kindergarten
thank you